Let's fly now.
Author        Tadatoshi Fujimaki
Published in Shounen Jump
Let's try now.
Let's
fly
now.
Get
my
stage!
Let's
try
now.
Next
my
stage!
Let's
fly
now.
Translation Check   AMS
Get
my
stage!
Let's
fly
now.
Now!
Running into the middle of that exciting stage...
mu
ne
o
do
ru
su
tee
ji
e
ka
ke
a
ga
ru
do
ma
nna
ka
de
K-Timing      Eternal Blizzard
Editing      AMS
Continually breakthrough your limits.
ka
gi
ri
na
ku
ri
n
ka
i
te
n
to
ppa
mi
se
te
yo
Timing       ninjacloud
We have dreams, we're fond of legends, everybody in the ring.
yu
me
ta
shi
na
mu
re
je
n
do
every
body
wa
no
na
ka
de
Don't hesitate, into the future, JUMP!
ma
yo
i
na
ku
mi
ra
i
e
no
JUMP
Typesetting      KmE, zegond
They all say they haven't fallen after they have.
o
chi
bu
re
te
na
i
to
o
chi
bu
re
te
ka
ra
i
u
ya
tsu
ba
kka
It's scary aiming at coming back from the dead but
ki
shi
ka
i
se
ne
ra
u
mi
chi
no
ri
ko
wa
ku
na
wa
i
ga
QC      muyg, sangofe,
ninjacloud
if the road is still blocked
ko
e
te
ku
ka
be
na
no
ni
tsu
u
ka
te
n
na
no
ni
Karaokes      KmE
after I've crossed all the barriers,
fu
sa
i
de
ru
na
ra
I need to realize I'm not alone.
hi
to
ri
ja
na
i
ji
ka
ku
o
Slam it!
t
o
d
k
e
We have to set the rim on fire!
w
e
h
a
v
e
t
o
m
a
k
e
a
R
I
M
F
I
R
E
Let's combine our power and our minds.
a
w
s
e
r
o
p
w
e
r
n
o
a
k
n
o
m
i
n
d
Encoding      Your Mom
We don't need any excuses.
i
w
a
k
e
i
r
a
n
z
o
Gotta dream, exceed your limits, and war.
G
o
t
a
d
r
e
a
m
g
e
n
k
a
i
t
o
w
a
r
I need to face up to my common sense,
ta
chi
ha
da
ka
ru
no
wa
ri
ka
i
shi
su
gi
ta
Kuroko's
I
(
)
I
(
)
Basketball
joushiki to
which I know all too well,
kodoku no maibotsu
and bury my loneliness.
RIM
FIRE!!
Come visit us at www.saizen-fansubs.com
My jumping power...
（火神(かがみ)）ジャンプ力…
それを生かすオレの戦い方
A style that utilizes that strength...
そんなもん 答えは１つだ 空中戦！
There's only one answer.
Aerial combat!
That's the only place I stand a chance against the Generation of Miracles!
“キセキの世代”と渡り合えるのは
そこしかねぇ
（火神）ん？ どした？
What's wrong?
You may be able to beat the Generation of Miracles in an aerial battle,
（黒子(くろこ)）火神君は—
“キセキの世代”に
空中戦なら勝てるかもしれません
but you may not be able to beat them on the ground.
けど
地上戦で勝てないかもしれません
それに ボクのパスも通用しません
My passes don't work against them.
If you can't do it, no one on Seirin stands a chance.
火神君がダメなら 今の誠凛(せいりん)で
相手をできる人はいません
But I just came up with something.
（黒子）けど 今 思いつきました
A way to help you and everyone on the team win...
火神君と みんなを 活(い)かすための
新しいボクのバスケ
My new style of basketball.
パス以外に
ボクだけのドライブを修得して—
By mastering my own drive in addition to my passes,
I will surpass the Generation of Miracles.
ボクが“キセキの世代”を抜きます
I won't lose, Aominecchi.
（黄瀬(きせ)）負けねっスよ 青峰(あおみね)っち
Have you ever beaten me before?
（青峰）今まで 一度でも
オレに勝ったことがあったかよ？
I really don't want to lose today.
（黄瀬）なんか
負けたくなくなっちゃったんスよ
ムショーに
Episode 23
I'm Not Mature
（女子生徒１）すごーい
That's amazing!
（女子生徒２）何ー？
What is?
It's the lifting test.
（女子生徒３）
リフティングのテストだって
Only Kise and Tanaka from the soccer team haven't dropped the ball once yet!
黄瀬君とサッカー部の田中(たなか)君だけ
全然 落ちないのー
203, 204, 205...
（教師）203 204 205…
I can already do this after watching someone for a bit.
（黄瀬）こんなん ちょっと見りゃ
すぐ できんじゃん
If anything, I can't believe there are guys who can't do this.
むしろ できないヤツのほうが
ナゼ！？ ってカンジだよ つーか…
He said we'd get an A if we lifted more than 100 times,
100回以上で 評価Ａって
言ってたし… もー いいや
so I guess I'm done.
Style is okay, athletics are okay,
（黄瀬）
スタイル オッケー 運動 オッケー
勉強も まあ オッケー
けど つまんねーなー
and academics are pretty okay, too.
But I'm so bored.
スポーツは好き だけど
やったら すぐ できちゃうし—
I like sports, but I always master them so quickly.
If I play long enough, there's no one left to challenge me.
しばらくやったら
相手がいなくなっちゃうんだよな…
Anybody, please, light a fire in me.
誰でもいいからさ
オレを燃えさせてください
I wonder if there's anyone so amazing that I don't stand a chance against him.
手も足も出ない
すごいヤツとか いないかなー
いんだろ どっか… 出てこいや！
He's got to be around somewhere.
Come on out.
なーんて…
Just kidding...
いったぁ！
Sorry, sorry.
（青峰）ワリーワリー
Hey, you're that famous model, Kise.
って モデルで有名な黄瀬君じゃん
What's your problem?
なんだよー
Thanks.
（青峰）サンキュー
（黄瀬）
バスケか まだ やったこと…
Basketball, huh?
I haven't tried that one yet.
そういや ウチの学校
かなり強いって聞いたことあるな
Now that I think of it, I heard our school is pretty strong.
Amazing!
（黄瀬）すっげえ…
あの速さで あの動き できるか！？
That speed, those movements...
Can I do that?
It's impossible. No, maybe if I try...
無理… いや 頑張れば
This is awesome.
やっべ いたよ すごいヤツ！
I found someone amazing!
Going forward, no matter how hard I try, I may never catch up to him.
（黄瀬）この先
オレが どんなに頑張っても—
追いつけないかもしれない
けど だからいい！
But that's just what I want!
I want to play basketball with this guy!
この人と バスケがしてみたい！
Someday... Someday...
そんで いつか… いつか
Not someday.
（黄瀬）いつか… じゃない
Today is the day.
もう 今が… そのときだ
The game's starting!
（伊月(いづき)）試合開始だ
It's Kaijo's ball first!
（日向(ひゅうが)）海常(かいじょう)ボールからか
How will they play?
（リコ）どう来る？
黄瀬君と青峰君 両方 戦って—
Having played against both Kise and Aomine,
正直な感想は 青峰君のほうが上
honestly speaking, I feel Aomine is better.
Forget the small stuff.
（笠松(かさまつ)）
いいんだよ こまけーことは
Our ace is...
それでも ウチのエースは 黄瀬だ！
Kise!
Kise versus Aomine!
（火神）
黄瀬 対 青峰！ いきなりかよっ！
They're already at it!
He broke past him!
（小金井(こがねい)）抜いたっ！
You're just as weak as you've always been.
相変わらず 甘(あめ)えな ツメが
You thought you could get past me with that?
そんなんで
抜けたと思っちまったのかよ
No, it's a steal!
（土田(つちだ)）ダメだ スティール！
Touou's on the counterattack!
（小金井）桐皇(とうおう)の反撃！
No. 8...
（若松(わかまつ)）８番 こいつ ディフェンス
地味な顔して やりやがる！
This guy's better at defense than he looks.
In that case...
なら…
Sorry!
（桜井(さくらい)）スイマセン！
（森山(もりやま)）ああっ
なんて クイックリリースだ…！
What a quick release!
（早川(はやかわ)）うおおおー イバーン！
Kaijo
Touou
（伊月）スリーポイント
A three pointer.
Looks like Touou scored first.
（木吉(きよし)）先制点は桐皇か
What? Kise again?
え！？ また黄瀬君！？
That's... What?
（桜井）って コレ… えええ！
（若松）桜井の
クイックシュートじゃねーか！
That's Sakurai's quick shot!
I see you're still good at copying people.
人マネは 相変わらず うめーな
が それじゃ 勝てねーよ！
But it's not enough to win!
He's fast!
（火神）速(はえ)ぇ！
あのボールに後出しで触れやがった
He got his hand on the ball even after jumping so late!
（伊月）いきなりエースが
立て続けに止められるのは—
It can't be good for them to have their ace stopped repeatedly already.
ヤバくねーか！？
If they score off this...
これでカウンター
もらったりしようもんなら…
We're in control of the game!
（今吉）流れは 一気にウチや！
なんやと！？
What?!
そんな簡単に流れをやるほど
お人好しじゃねーよ！
We're not generous enough to hand over control that easily!
Kaijo
Touou
They're tied!
（土田）同点！
Defense! Let's stop them!
よし ディフェンス！
１本 止めんぞ！
Yeah!
（海常選手たち）おう！！
He made a sudden shot from there?
（日向）あそこで いきなり打って
決めるのかよ！
He could have regrouped before attacking.
立て直して
キッチリ攻めてもいい場面で—
すかさず返して
流れをぶった切った！
But he got them right back and broke their control!
We'll follow up on you as much as you need!
フォローぐれぇ いくらでも
してやる ガンガン行け！
Keep going!
Senpai...
先輩…
I didn't say you could let them stop you though!
けど ガンガンやられていいとは
言ってねぇ！
スンマセン！ うわぁ〜 ああっ
Sorry!
（若松）つーか テンション
上げてきてるぜ こいつらぁ！
These guys are getting fired up!
むしろ 流れを…
They're trying to take control.
They've almost taken control of the game.
（原澤(はらさわ)）持っていかれかけてますね
Kasamatsu, is it?
笠松君… ですか
He's got good leadership skills.
大したキャプテンシーだ
そうそう いないですよ
There aren't many guys like him.
が 彼を止めないかぎり
流れは切れない
As long as we don't stop him,
we won't be able to take control.
なるほど 頼りになる先輩だな
I see. What a dependable senior.
“１人じゃダメでも
みんなでなら 戦えるっス”ってか
If you can't fight me yourself, you'll fight me all at once, huh?
You've started thinking like Tetsu.
テツみてーなこと
考えるようになったな
Did you have a change of heart after losing to him?
負けて心変わりでも
したか？ 眠たくなるぜ
You're putting me to sleep.
（黄瀬）ハァ？ そんなこと
一言も言ってないっスよ？
What?
I didn't say anything like that.
Bastard!
（青峰）こいつ！
They have no openings. Their defense is good.
（木吉）
スキがない… いいディフェンスだ
I guess I've come to acknowledge Kurokocchi's way of thinking.
（黄瀬）まぁ 確かに 黒子っちの
考え方も 認めるようになったっス
I even want to help Kaijo win.
海常を勝たせたい気持ち
なんてのも 出てきた
But I don't care what's correct.
けど 何が正論かなんて
今は どーでもいいんスよ
オレは アンタを倒したいんだよ
I just want to beat you.
I'm not mature enough to play basketball with reason over instinct!
理屈で 本能 抑えて
バスケやれるほど—
大人じゃねーよ！
Bring it on.
やってみな！
（火神）身体能力だけでいえば
黄瀬は 青峰に負けてねー
When it comes to physical ability,
Kise's not any worse than Aomine.
But I'm still not sure he can beat Aomine one-on-one.
だけど 速さと それを生かした
青峰のワンオンワンを止めるなんて
A pass?
パス！？
（火神）なんて切り返しだ！
What a crossover!
すっげぇ あの速さを止めたぁ！？
Amazing! He stopped him!
No, it's not over yet.
いえ… まだです
（火神）フォームレスシュート！
A formless shot!
マジかよ…
Seriously?
（河原(かわはら)）おぉぉぉー！
He completely...
（降旗(ふりはた)）完ペキに…
stopped...
（福田(ふくだ)）あの青峰を…
Aomine!
（１年生たち）止めたぁ！
Kuroko's
I
Basketball
（河原）うぉぉ スゲェー！
Amazing!
He stopped Aomine!
（降旗）青峰を止めたー！
I'm impressed.
（今吉(いまよし)）さすがに たまげたで
ワンオンワンで青峰 止めたヤツ
初めて見たわ
That's the first time I've seen anyone stop Aomine one-on-one.
I didn't think you'd actually stop me.
まさか マジで止めるとはよ
青峰っちと
毎日 ワンオンワンやって—
Who do you think played and lost to you one-on-one every day?
毎日 負けてたのは
誰だと思ってんスか
I know you better than anyone else.
アンタのことは
オレが 一番 よく知ってる
I see.
なるほど
（黄瀬）青峰っち！ 勝負っス！
Aominecchi! Let's play!
てぇっ… もっかい！ もっかい！
One more game! One more game!
No way! I'm done for today.
やーだよ！ 今日は終わりだ
もう何時だと思ってんだよ
What time do you think it is?
Damn it...
（黄瀬）くっそー！
Damn, I'm smiling. He really is strong.
（黄瀬）
ヤッベ ニヤける やっぱ 強(つえ)え…
But losing still sucks!
けど くやしいもんは くやしい！
It hurts, but I'm having fun.
苦しくて楽しい
フッ… なんだろ この感じ
What is this feeling?
Why don't you go a little easier on him?
（さつき）もうちょっと
手加減してあげれば？
Kise's never played before.
黄瀬君 初心者なんだから
Go easy on him?
手加減だあ？
そんな余裕ねぇよ
I can't afford to do that.
Momoi... Momoi...
（原澤）桃井(ももい)さん…
桃井さん… 桃井さん
Momoi...
What? I'm sorry.
え！？ あっ スミマセン！
Did you give Aomine Kise's data?
青峰君に 黄瀬君のデータ
渡してありますか？
すみません
それが どうしても受け取らなくて
I'm sorry. He refused to accept it.
Then defending may prove a little tricky.
じゃあ ディフェンスも
一筋縄では いかなそうですね
いえ 大丈夫です
No, we'll be fine.
I gave the data to the other four.
他の４人には渡してあります
今までのデータも…
Their past data and...
これからのデータも
their future data.
He stopped Aomine,
（日向）青峰は止めた
が 桐皇の強さは もう１つ—
but Touou has another strength.
Momoi's precognitive defense.
桃井の先読みディフェンス
（笠松）どうする！？ 黄瀬に…
What should we do? Should I pass to Kise?
森山！
Moriyama!
We won't fall for that!
（今吉）かからんで！ そこで
パスと見せかけてのドライブやろ！
You're going to fake a pass...
and try to drive it!
They knew?
読んでる！？
You're wrong!
（笠松）
違うね！ 本命は このあと…
I'm really going for what's coming next.
The turnaround!
ターンアラウンド！
Into a fadeaway jumper!
からの
ファイダウェイジャンパー やろ？
（降旗）うわあ これも読んでる
He knew he'd do that too!
You're right, but it doesn't matter!
当たり けど 関係ねぇな！
He's fast! You're kidding!
（今吉）速い！ ウソや！？
先 読んで 追いつけへんやと！？
I knew it was coming, but I couldn't keep up!
（笠松）
チッ… 爪 かすりやがった
He got a finger on it.
Rebound!
（笠松）リバン！
I'll get it this time!
今度こそっ… イッバァーン！
Crap, the offense got the rebound.
（諏佐(すさ)）
しまった オフェンスリバウンド
This guy...
（若松）こいつ…
Shut up already!
つうか うっせ！
His form is unique. It's almost strange!
（桜井）この人のフォームって
独特っていうか… 変！
His spin is terrible, but his shots still go in!
回転も悪いし
でも これ… 入る！？
（アナウンス）
第１クオーター 終了です
The first quarter is over.
Kaijo
Touou
流れは 完全に海常ね
Kaijo completely took the first quarter.
Aomine's not holding back again, is he?
まさか 青峰 また
手ぇ抜いてたりしねぇだろうな？
No, he must be trying.
（黒子）いえ 恐らく本気です
黄瀬君が それを上回ってるとしか
I can only assume Kise is beating him.
Listen to me, Aomine. At this rate...
やっぱり 聞いて 青峰君
このままじゃ…
うっせーよ さつき… ふぃー
Shut up, Satsuki.
Kise's gotten stronger.
（青峰）
強くなったなぁ 黄瀬… ヤベェわ
I'm in trouble.
Good job, everyone!
（武内）よぉーし 全員いいぞ！
黄瀬も いいカンジだ
Kise, you're doing well too!
We're not losing to Aomine. At this rate...
青峰に負けてねぇよ これなら…
I don't know about that.
いや どうスかね？
このままいけたら 苦労はないっス
If we won like this, it would be too easy.
Kaijo's in the lead.
海常リード… 正直 驚いたな
Honestly, I'm surprised.
Yeah.
I didn't expect Kise to beat Aomine this badly.
（火神）黄瀬が
ここまで 青峰を圧倒するなんて
He's definitely gotten stronger.
確実に強くなっている
Can I ask you something?
（木吉）ひとつ いいか？
（一同）うん？
How did you guys beat Kaijo?
オマエら
どーやって 海常に勝ったの？
Um...
気合い… とか？
With spirit?
あと…
青峰君が本気とは言いましたが—
Also, while I said Aomine is trying,
he tends to get stronger as the game goes on.
彼は 尻上がりに
調子を上げていく傾向があります
If he's going to get any better,
そして 上げるとしたら
そろそろだと思います
it will probably happen soon.
うぉぉぉぉ！
よぉーし！ いくぞー！
All right! Let's go!
Let's do it! Let's get those rebounds!
やうぞー！
とっうぞー イバウンドォ！
I'm ready to go! Yeah!
やう気 全開ー！ しゃー！
That guy won't shut up!
つーか
さっきから うるせーよ あいつ！
You're always pretty loud too.
いや オマエも
いつも 結構 うっさいで
What?
You're actually quite similar.
（諏佐）むしろ 似てる
You're kidding!
ウソォ！？
Anyway, it's no fun watching your opponents celebrate.
（今吉）ま… なんにせよ 浮かれる
敵さん見ても おもろくはないなぁ
Let's take it slow, shall we?
ボチボチいこか
I thought they'd play more aggressively from the start,
（日向）もっと 開始から
ガンガンくるかと思ったら—
but they're pretty quiet.
静かな立ち上がりだな
There it is!
（降旗）来たあ！
（福田）
第２クオーター まずは桐皇！
Touou scored the first basket of the second quarter!
Calm down!
落ち着け！
１本 キッチリ返すぞ！
Let's get that back!
（笠松）こいつ…
This guy...
I know you're fast, so I'm not letting you go.
もう 速いのは分かったわ
それを踏まえて いかせへんで！
Let me tell you one more thing.
あと１つ 忠告しとくわ
誰が相手でも青峰は負けん
No matter who he's up against, Aomine doesn't lose.
He's the best.
最強はあいつや
Such pressure!
（黄瀬）この圧力！
（火神）ここまで ビシビシ伝わる
すげえ集中力だ！
I can feel it all the way up here!
Their focus is intense!
I don't know what you're planning, but our Kise...
何 たくらんでんのか 知らねーが
ウチの黄瀬だって
ハハッ… たくらむ？
そんなもん あらへんよ
Planning?
We don't have anything like that.
たくらみなんてもんは
ワイらみたいな小物がやることや
Planning is something small fries like you do.
格の差や 単純にな
Put simply, it's a difference in skill.
There are plenty of reasons for it.
理由なんぞ いくらでもある
例えば…
For example...
Otherworldly agility!
敏しょう性… アジリティー
He knows what I'm planning?
（黄瀬）読まれてる!?
いや それより… 速いっ
No, he's just fast!
You said you know me better than anyone.
（青峰）“オレのことを 一番
よく知ってる”って言ったか？
Did you think it didn't work the other way around?
逆は考えなかったのか？
From the left...
（黄瀬）
左… から右へのクロスオーバー！
A crossover to the right!
I stopped him!
止めた！
No... The other way?
そんな… 逆！？
And then there's skill.
そして スキル
Seriously?
（火神）マジかよ？ 読み合いでは
黄瀬が勝ってたはずが—
Kise should have had the advantage.
By manipulating Kise's center of gravity, he turned the tables!
黄瀬の重心の変化から
強引に もう１つ 切り返した！？
Don't foul, Kobori!
ファウルは よせ 小堀(こぼり)！
Basket counts! And one!
（審判）バスケットカウント！
ワンスロー！
He made the shot!
（河原）決めた！
How did that go in?
（福田）
なんで あれが入るんだ！？
（小堀）すまん…
Sorry.
気にすんな すぐ切り替えろ
Don't worry about it.
Get ready for the next play.
Kaijo
Touou
They're tied!
（降旗）同点！
Kaijo
Touou
Touou quickly closed the gap!
Kaijo
Touou
（河原）
桐皇が一気に追い上げてきた！
Kaijo
Touou
This isn't good.
（日向）まずい 青峰が
抑えきれなくなってきた 強(つえ)ぇ…
They can't stop Aomine anymore.
He's too strong.
Not even Kise can beat him.
やっぱり 黄瀬でも 勝てないのか
また？
Again?
Kaijo must intend to put everything on Kise.
海常は 黄瀬君で とことん行く気ね
You still don't understand.
分からん人やなぁ
Your Kise's good at copying people, but that's it.
おたくの黄瀬君 人マネは
上手いみたいやけど そんだけや
It's the biggest reason Kise can't win.
黄瀬君が勝てん最大の理由
He doesn't have his own weapon.
彼だけの武器がない
It's impossible for him to beat Aomine at basketball.
ただのバスケで
青峰に勝つのは不可能や
（笠松）なぁ あんた よく
“性格 悪い”って言われねーか
Say, do a lot of people tell you you've got a bad personality?
Whoa, now. That's pretty harsh.
おっとぉ いきなり キビシーやんけ
You're the one who doesn't understand.
分かってねぇのは
あんたのほうだよ
Copying techniques and making them your own is learning.
技術をマネて身につけることは
学ぶってこと
In other words, it's growing.
つまり 成長するってことだ
（青峰）こいつ…
This guy...
He's copying Kasamatsu this time.
今度は 笠松と同じ動きか
But...
（青峰）が 残念だったな
Too bad!
I'm the one marking you.
オマエのマークは このオレだぜ？
Don't assume I'm like that evil glasses guy.
あっちの腹黒メガネと
一緒にすんなよ
Are you talking about me?
それって ワシのこと！？ ヒドッ！
So mean!
Kaijo High School, time out.
（アナウンス）
海常高校 タイムアウトです
Kaijo
Touou
They're tied.
Kaijo
Touou
（日向）同点か… けど こっからだ
Kaijo
Touou
But the game's just getting started.
Touou won't be easy to stop once they get going.
勢いに乗った桐皇は ちょっとや
そっとじゃ 止めらんねーぞ
But the difference between the two teams isn't much.
（木吉）とはいえ
両チームの差は そこまでない
Victory will be decided by the difference between their aces.
勝敗を分けるとしたら
エースの差か… どうする？
What will they do?
Kuroko?
黒子？
ハァー
Just like I thought, Aominecchi is amazing.
（黄瀬）思ったとおり
やっぱ 青峰っちは スゲー
If we don't prepare ourselves, we're screwed.
こりゃ いよいよ
覚悟 決めなきゃ マズイっスね
Quick turnarounds are their specialty.
（武内）いいか
早い展開は 向こうの十八番(おはこ)だ
Don't match their pace.
向こうのペースに合わせるな
あと インサイド…
Also, the inside...
Coach.
監督…
That thing I mentioned before the game...
（黄瀬）試合前に言ってたアレ…
やっぱ やらせてほしいっス
I want you to let me do it.
Honnouteki naru situation
An instinctive situation,
tatakau imi o sagasu kono imitation
searching for a reason to fight this imitation.
Kurayami kara koboreru raito
Use the light that seeps from the darkness,
torawareta yourself kowase
and break free from your imprisonment.
Jiyuu ukeirete wa mogaite kuratte fuantei
Accept your freedom and struggle through your insecurities.
Kodou ga boku o tsukiage spy kidottenda
The pulsation throws me for a loop and I begin to spy.
Bring back the Catalyst "a simple way to best"
Bring back the Catalyst "a simple way to best."
And Rhythm like this never ends
And Rhythm like this never ends.
Sometimes your voice reached to me
Sometimes your voice reached to me,
Because I don't want to face the fate
because I dont want to face the fate.
Tobi tachitaku naru tte?
You say you wanna jump back up?
Katarurizumu oboete ndarou
You remember the catal rhythm, don't you?
Mune ni hibiku akirame no kako e
To the past resounding resignation in your chest,
Sabita sukoaboodo mitai ni
like a rusty scoreboard,
kimi mo koko de furuete ndarou?
you're shaking, aren't you?
Toriaezu wa mayoi no nai mirai e
For now, confidently head into the future.
Zanzou demo ii nda
Even if it's just a fragment of yourself.
Future aspect
Next Episode
（黄瀬）青峰っちに勝ちたい
I want to beat Aominecchi.
（青峰）オレのコピー？
Copy me?
Even if you manage to do it, it won't change anything.
できたとしても
結果は変わんねーんだよ
I don't want to lose to you, Aominecchi.
（黄瀬）
青峰っちに負けてほしくない
（青峰）
オレに勝てるのは オレだけだ
The only one who can beat me is me.
（黄瀬）憧れるのは もう やめる
I give up on looking up to you.
Episode 24
Don't Get the Wrong Idea